Guide to the Mix Collection, 1970-2014 (Bulk 1987-2001) MSS.143
Fales Library and Special Collections
- SERIES XIV: 2000, 116992
  - Subseries G: Media, 116995
    - Title: Kiss XXX, Screened: 2000; 117128 (Box 66, Folder ID: 143.0353)
      Director: Shimazaki, Akira
    - Title: Mathi, Screened: 2000; 117127 (Box 66, Folder ID: 143.0354)
      Old number: 00-046
      Director: Lenin, B.
    - Title: Illusion, Screened: 2000; 117126 (Box 66, Folder ID: 143.0355)
      Old number: 00-048
      Director: Nam, Alfonso
    - Title: Annie Sprinkle's Herstory of Porn, Screened: 2000; 117125 (Box 66, Folder ID: 143.0356)
      Old number: 00-049
      Director: Sprinkle, Annie and Scarlot Harlot
      Duration: [80] minutes
    - Title: Infidel, Screened: 2000; 117124 (Box 66, Folder ID: 143.0357)
      Old number: 00-051
      Director: Richter, Suzy
    - Title: Ariel, Screened: 2000; 117123 (Box 66, Folder ID: 143.0358)
      Old number: 00-052
      Director: Moore, Glen
    - Title: Tutti Frutti, Screened: 2000; 117122 (Box 66, Folder ID: 143.0359)
      Old number: 00-054
      Director: DiLorenzo, Joseph R.
    - Title: The Tell-Tale Vibrator, Screened: 2000; 117121 (Box 66, Folder ID: 143.0360)
      Old number: 00-056
      Director: Chamberlain, Jill
    - Title: Night Deposit, Screened: 2000; 117120 (Box 66, Folder ID: 143.0361)
      Old number: 00-061
      Director: Mitchell, Monika
      Duration: 10 minutes8
    - Title: One, Screened: 2000; 117119 (Box 66, Folder ID: 143.0362)
      Old number: 00-069
      Director: [Sophia, Alma]
    - Title: Cloud Seeding Promo Video, Screened: 2000; 117118 (Box 66, Folder ID: 143.0363)
      Old number: 00-068
    - Title: Mes Deux Histoires, Screened: 2000; 117117 (Box 66, Folder ID: 143.0364)
      Old number: 00-062
      Director: Messman, Kevin
    - Title: While Ending Silence, Screened: 2000; 117116 (Box 66, Folder ID: 143.0365)
      Old number: 00-067
      Director: Selinger, Liv and Leena McCarthy
    - Title: Dime a Dozen, Screened: 2000; 117115 (Box 66, Folder ID: 143.0366)
      Old number: 00-070
      Director: Torke, Ann
    - Title: Restroom, Screened: 2000; 117114 (Box 66, Folder ID: 143.0367)
      Old number: 00-072
      Director: Hildebran, Gretchen
    - Title: New York Is Disappearing, Screened: 2000; 117113 (Box 66, Folder ID: 143.0368)
      Old number: 00-074
    - Title: The Edge of Each Other's Battles: The Vision of Audre Lorde, Screened: 2000; 117112 (Box 66, Folder ID: 143.0369)
      Old number: 00-076
      Director: Abod, Jennifer
    - Title: Two Brides and a Scalpel: Diary of a Lesbian Marriage, Screened: 2000; 117111 (Box 66, Folder ID: 143.0370)
      Old number: 00-078
      Director: Achbar, Mark
      Duration: 66 minutes
    - Title: Automatic, Screened: 2000; 117110 (Box 66, Folder ID: 143.0371)
      Old number: 00-084
    - Title: Third Degree, Screened: 2000; 117109 (Box 66, Folder ID: 143.0372)
      Old number: 00-085
      Director: Lynch, Mary
    - Title: http.www.tubeandmemory.hk/love.97, Screened: 2000; 117108 (Box 66, Folder ID: 143.0373)
      Old number: 00-091
      Director: Keung, Hung
    - Title: Annie Complex, Screened: 2000; 117107 (Box 66, Folder ID: 143.0374)
      Old number: 00-092
      Director: Goldate, Stacy and KJ Mohr
    - Title: Diary of Indulgence, Screened: 2000; 117106 (Box 67, Folder ID: 143.0375)
      Old number: 00-099
      Director: Etzkorn, CJ
    - Title: "Bra Strap" Far from Hollywood, Screened: 2000; 117105 (Box 67, Folder ID: 143.0376)
      Old number: 00-110
      Director: Crawford, Nagano
    - Title: The Making of a Concept Documentary, Series: "For Women Only: Women to Women", Screened: 2000; 117104 (Box 67, Folder ID: 143.0377)
      Old number: 00-111
      Director: Dulinsky, Jack Roberts
    - Title: Women, Screened: 2000; 117103 (Box 67, Folder ID: 143.0378)
      Old number: 00-116
      Director: Akiva, Maia
    - Title: I Love Sex, Screened: 2000; 117102 (Box 67, Folder ID: 143.0379)
      Old number: 00-118
      Director: Mars, Shelly
    - Title: The Deal, Screened: 2000; 117101 (Box 67, Folder ID: 143.0380)
      Old number: 00-120
      Director: Girolami, Lisa
    - Title: The Cucumber Chronicles, Screened: 2000; 117100 (Box 67, Folder ID: 143.0381)
      Old number: 00-121
      Director: McHenry, Bryan
    - Title: (I'm Living) A Charmed Life, Screened: 2000; 117099 (Box 67, Folder ID: 143.0382)
      Old number: 00-122
    - Title: Loved by You, Screened: 2000; 117098 (Box 67, Folder ID: 143.0383)
      Old number: 00-125
      Director: Parker, Steve
    - Title: Asleep, Screened: 2000; 117097 (Box 67, Folder ID: 143.0384)
      Old number: 00-126
    - Title: Strangelove, Screened: 2000; 117096 (Box 67, Folder ID: 143.0385)
      Old number: 00-149
      Director: Nadeau, James
    - Title: Sparked!, Screened: 2000; 117095 (Box 67, Folder ID: 143.0386)
      Old number: 00-153
      Director: Hadley, Lisa Marie and Carrazana, J.
    - Title: Post Mortem (doc. of 2-channel video installation), Screened: 2000; 117094 (Box 67, Folder ID: 143.0387)
      Old number: 00-154
    - Title: Knocked Out, Screened: 2000; 117093 (Box 67, Folder ID: 143.0388)
      Old number: 00-161
      Director: de Simone, Sean
    - Title: Once and Future Queen, Screened: 2000; 117092 (Box 67, Folder ID: 143.0389)
      Old number: 00-162
      Director: Verow, Todd
    - Title: The Rape of Ganymede, Screened: 2000; 117091 (Box 67, Folder ID: 143.0390)
      Old number: 00-164
      Director: Whitman, Tom and Dustin Woehrmann
    - Title: Queens for a Night, Screened: 2000; 117090 (Box 67, Folder ID: 143.0391)
      Old number: 00-166
      Director: Gomersall, Christopher
    - Title: Cannibal Garden Video Installation, Screened: 2000; 117089 (Box 67, Folder ID: 143.0392)
      Old number: 00-169
    - Title: Breeder Feeders, Screened: [2000]; 117088 (Box 67, Folder ID: 143.0393)
      Old number: 00-171
      Director: [Regina]
    - Title: My Life as a Dog at the Gym, Screened: 2000; 117087 (Box 67, Folder ID: 143.0394)
      Old number: 00-172
      Director: Supermarky de Sage [Chris Maher]
    - Title: Mujeres Calladas, Screened: 2000; 117086 (Box 67, Folder ID: 143.0395)
      Old number: 00-174
      Director: Kelly, Christina
    - Title: Eating Cherries, Screened: 2000; 117085 (Box 67, Folder ID: 143.0396)
      Old number: 00-173
      Director: Maher, Chris / Supermarky de Sage
    - Title: I Think I'm Beautiful…, Screened: 2000; 117084 (Box 67, Folder ID: 143.0397)
      Old number: 00-183
      Director: Velky, Stephen
    - Title: Who Needs Hollywood!, Screened: 2000; 117083 (Box 67, Folder ID: 143.0398)
      Old number: 00-177
      Director: Rota, Nina
    - Title: I Am Your Sister, Screened: 2000; 117082 (Box 67, Folder ID: 143.0399)
      Old number: 00-176
      Director: Britton, Lashambi
    - Title: Life's a Butch!, Screened: 2000; 117081 (Box 67, Folder ID: 143.0400)
      Old number: 00-175
      Director: Goodman, A. Rosser
    - Title: Dykes and Their Dogs, Screened: 2000; 117080 (Box 67, Folder ID: 143.0401)
      Old number: 00-184
      Director: Sotile, Renee and Mary Jo Godges
    - Title: Gay Marriage: A One Man Show, Screened: 2000; 117079 (Box 68, Folder ID: 143.0402)
      Old number: 00-195
    - Title: Erika in Amerika, Screened: 2000; 117078 (Box 68, Folder ID: 143.0403)
      Old number: 00-189
      Director: Baehr, Antonia
    - Title: Verbal Sex: The Art of Nyna, Screened: 2000; 117077 (Box 68, Folder ID: 143.0404)
      Old number: 00-198
      Director: Ferreras, Alberto
    - Title: Lost in the Pershing Point Hotel, Screened: 2000; 117076 (Box 68, Folder ID: 143.0405)
      Old number: 00-199
      Director: Pierrepon, Julia Jay
    - Title: The Visit, Screened: 2000; 117075 (Box 68, Folder ID: 143.0406)
      Old number: 00-200
      Director: Afnan, Shahin
    - Title: Bone Wish, Screened: 2000; 117074 (Box 68, Folder ID: 143.0407)
      Old number: 00-206
      Director: Severance, Abigail
    - Title: Beautiful Girl, Screened: 2000; 117073 (Box 68, Folder ID: 143.0408)
      Old number: 00-207
      Director: Greenwell, Erin
    - Title: Wonder Woman: Battle With the Basher, Screened: 2000; 117072 (Box 68, Folder ID: 143.0409)
      Old number: 00-229
      Director: Curran, Gary and Brian Winkowski
    - Title: Short Memory / No History (preview version #3), Screened: 2000; 117071 (Box 68, Folder ID: 143.0410)
      Old number: 00-237
      Director: Waters, Jaack and Peter Cramer
    - Title: Pop Tarts, Screened: 2000; 117070 (Box 68, Folder ID: 143.0411)
      Old number: 00-255
    - Title: Beautiful Girl, Screened: 2000; 117069 (Box 68, Folder ID: 143.0412)
      Old number: 00-238
    - Title: Sexotheque (2 promos, 2 commercials), Screened: 2000; 117068 (Box 68, Folder ID: 143.0413)
      Old number: 00-256
      Director: Phillips, J. Todd
    - Title: A Bit of Scarlet, Screened: 2000; 117067 (Box 68, Folder ID: 143.0414)
      Old number: 00-258
      Director: Weiss, Andrea
    - Title: Nicolas, Screened: 2000; 117066 (Box 68, Folder ID: 143.0415)
      Old number: 00-273
    - Title: Stepdown, Screened: 2000; 117065 (Box 68, Folder ID: 143.0416)
      Old number: 00-298
      Director: Mattes, Craig
    - Title: Tranny Fag Action, Screened: 2000; 117064 (Box 68, Folder ID: 143.0417)
      Old number: 00-276
      Director: Parriott, Olivia
    - Title: Flythrough (loop), Screened: Unknown; 117063 (Box 68, Folder ID: 143.0418)
    - Title: Old School vs. New School, Screened: 2000; 117062 (Box 68, Folder ID: 143.0419)
    - Title: Mix 99 Trailer, Screened: 2000; 117061 (Box 68, Folder ID: 143.0420)
      Director: [Stanley, Anie]
    - Title: Taking Back the Y, Screened: 2000; 117060 (Box 68, Folder ID: 143.0421)
      Director: Peyton, Michael and Richard Shurtliff
    - Title: Skin, Screened: 2000; 117059 (Box 68, Folder ID: 143.0422)
      Director: Jarvis, Ian and David Collins
    - Title: Lost Portraits, Screened: 2000; 117058 (Box 68, Folder ID: 143.0423)
    - Title: The Ride, Screened: 2000; 117057 (Box 69, Folder ID: 143.0449)
      Old number: 00-157
      Director: Smolen, Wayne or Basquin, Bill
    - Title: Major Repair Job, Screened: 1998, 2000; 117056 (Box 69, Folder ID: 143.0450)
      Old number: 00-047
      Director: Cholwich, Pepe and Armando Sepulveda
    - Title: Mix 2000 Transrendered Showcase: [1.]--Light My Fire [2.]--Guileless Guile [3.]--Mad About the Boy [4.]--Cucumber Chronicles [5.]--Digital Penis.., Screened: 2000; 117055 (Box 69, Folder ID: 143.0451)
      Director: [3.]--Umen, Alix and Banker, Lisel
    - Title: Slean and Villegas, Screened: 2000; 117054 (Box 69, Folder ID: 143.0452)
      Old number: 00-089
    - Title: The Cucumber Chronicles, Screened: 2000; 117053 (Box 69, Folder ID: 143.0453)
    - Title: Mix 2000 Teen Beat and Transrendered Showcase, Screened: 2000; 117052 (Box 69, Folder ID: 143.0454)
    - Title: [1.]--Oppression [2.]--Bousculade 1 [3.]--Bousculade 2 [4.]-- Suspension [5.]-- Liens, Screened: 2000; 117051 (Box 69, Folder ID: 143.0455)
      Old number: 00-038, 00-039
      Director: Blanchard, Beatrice
    - Title: Changing Faces, Screened: 2000; 117050 (Box 69, Folder ID: 143.0456)
      Old number: 00-040
      Director: Haegelin, Marinell
    - Title: Melt, Screened: 2000; 117049 (Box 69, Folder ID: 143.0458)
      Old number: 00-217
      Director: Birkhead, Cyndi
    - Title: Stepdown, Screend: 2000; 117048 (Box 69, Folder ID: 143.0459)
      Director: Matters, Craig
    - Title: [1.]--Quirks [2.]--Cosmic, Screened: 2000; 117047 (Box 69, Folder ID: 143.0460)
      Old number: 00-208, 00-209
      Director: Ebmeier, Dave
    - Title: Mujeres Calladas, Screened: 2000; 117046 (Box 69, Folder ID: 143.0461)
    - Title: devOur: the phOtOgrapher uncOnsciOus, Screened: 2000; 117045 (Box 69, Folder ID: 143.0462)
      Old number: 00-071
      Director: Wengertsman, Dave
    - Title: David, Screened: 2000; 117044 (Box 69, Folder ID: 143.0463)
      Old number: 00-055
      Director: Swift, Chia-Hui Gao
    - Title: An Intimate Friendship, Screened: 2000; 117043 (Box 69, Folder ID: 143.0464)
      Old number: 00-028
      Director: Hughey, Angela and Charmaine Klohe
    - Title: Taking Back the Y, Screened: 2000; 117042 (Box 69, Folder ID: 143.0465)
      Old number: 00-112
      Director: Payton, Michael and Richard Shurtliff
    - Title: Meeting Mr. Crisp, Screened: 2000; 117041 (Box 69, Folder ID: 143.0466)
      Old number: 00-060
      Director: Evans, Nathan
    - Title: Once and Future Queen, Screened: 2000; 117040 (Box 69, Folder ID: 143.0467)
    - Title: Fine China, Screened: 2000; 117039 (Box 69, Folder ID: 143.0468)
      Old number: 00-188
    - Title: The Cucumber Chronicles, Screened: 2000; 117038 (Box 69, Folder ID: 143.0469)
    - Title: Mix 2000 Time Warp Program: [1.]--Footprints [2.]--Gay Marriage, A One-Man Show [3.]--Wonder Woman: Battle With the Basher, Screened: 2000; 117037 (Box 69, Folder ID: 143.0470)
    - Title: The B-Reel, Screened: 2000; 117036 (Box 69, Folder ID: 143.0471)
      Old number: 00-045
    - Title: The Window, Screened: 2000; 117035 (Box 69, Folder ID: 143.0472)
      Old number: 00-005
    - Title: Mix 2000 The Third Sexers Program, Screened: 2000; 117034 (Box 69, Folder ID: 143.0473)
    - Title: Plague, Screened: 2000; 117033 (Box 69, Folder ID: 143.0474)
      Old number: 00-156
      Director: Mansmann, Christa
    - Title: TSTHN, Screened: 2000; 117032 (Box 69, Folder ID: 143.0475)
      Old number: 00-272
      Director: Krach, Aaron
    - Title: The Jaguar and the Giraffe, Screened: 2000; 117031 (Box 70, Folder ID: 143.0476)
      Old number: 00-165
    - Title: Tabula Rasa, Screened: 2000; 117030 (Box 70, Folder ID: 143.0477)
      Old number: 00-079
      Director: Polli, Janet
    - Title: Mix 2000: Digifest Dupe Tape, Screened: 2000; 117029 (Box 70, Folder ID: 143.0478)
    - Title: Super Duper, Screened: 2000; 117028 (Box 70, Folder ID: 143.0479)
      Old number: 00-236
      Director: Koelher, Kurt
    - Title: Ghost Limb Films: The Trailer, Screened: 2000; 117027 (Box 70, Folder ID: 143.0480)
    - Title: Back Story, Screened: 2000; 117026 (Box 70, Folder ID: 143.0481)
      Old number: 00-002
      Director: Matthews, John Scott
    - Title: Rancour, Screened: 2000; 117025 (Box 70, Folder ID: 143.0482)
      Director: Earl, Karen
    - Title: Mad About the Boy, Screened: 2000; 117024 (Box 70, Folder ID: 143.0483)
      Old number: 00-009
      Director: Calpe, Alan
    - Title: Twisted Fate, Screened: 2000; 117023 (Box 70, Folder ID: 143.0484)
      Old number: 00-083
      Director: Venegas, Maurizio
    - Title: Traditional Family Vampires, Screened: 2000; 117022 (Box 70, Folder ID: 143.0485)
      Old number: 00-170
      Director: Roger, Bobby
    - Title: Haunt #451, Screened: 2000; 117021 (Box 70, Folder ID: 143.0486)
      Old number: 00-033
      Director: Donovan, Susana
    - Title: Ah Leon, Screened: 2000; 117020 (Box 70, Folder ID: 143.0487)
      Old number: 00-001
    - Title: Override, Screened: 2000; 117019 (Box 70, Folder ID: 143.0489)
      Old number: 00-081
      Director: Ginsburg, Lisa
    - Title: Stalking Mike Hawke, Screened: 2000 (?); 117018 (Box 70, Folder ID: 143.0490)
    - Title: Kinky Pinkys, Screened: 2000; 117017 (Box 70, Folder ID: 143.0491)
      Old number: 00-235
      Director: Weide, Darlene
    - Title: Poem in Light, Screened: 2000; 117016 (Box 70, Folder ID: 143.0492)
      Old number: 00-181
      Director: [Pasolim, Lobo] and Prashker, Ian
    - Title: Afternoon Memory, Screened: 2002; 117015 (Box 70, Folder ID: 143.0493)
      Old number: 00-117
      Director: Goguen, Christen
    - Title: Mix 2000 Autopsy Program, Screened: 2000; 117014 (Box 70, Folder ID: 143.0494)
    - Title: The Nerve of You, Screened: 2000; 117013 (Box 70, Folder ID: 143.0495)
      Old number: 00-057
      Director: [Ghianni],, Jolie
    - Title: Homecoming Queens, Screened: 2000; 117012 (Box 70, Folder ID: 143.0496)
      Old number: 00-230
    - Title: In all of this world what is the one thing you most want?, Screened: 2000; 117011 (Box 70, Folder ID: 143.0497)
      Old number: 00-152
      Director: LeMieux, Curt
    - Title: [1.]--Aren't You Lucky You Brought Your Own Chair? [2.]--Sexual Exiles [x2 loop], Screened: 2000; 117010 (Box 70, Folder ID: 143.0498)
    - Title: Little Voices That Speak from a Box: A Montage of Memories, Screened: 2000; 117009 (Box 70, Folder ID: 143.0499)
      Old number: 00-100
      Director: Wollore, Joanne
    - Title: [1.]--MLK [2.]--Dancing [3.]--Faces, Screened: 2000; 117008 (Box 70, Folder ID: 143.0500)
      Old number: 00-130, 00-131, 00-132
      Director: [CBCooke]
    - Title: Manipulation (you've got pics), Screened: 2000; 117007 (Box 70, Folder ID: 143.0501)
      Old number: 00-296
    - Title: scopOphilic: Manhattan Neighborhood Network (Public Access TV), Screened: 2000; 117006 (Box 71, Folder ID: 143.0502)
      Old number: 00-133
    - Title: Safe Sex, Screened: 2000; 117005 (Box 71, Folder ID: 143.0503)
      Old number: 00-197
      Director: Griffith, Chuck
    - Title: The Journey of Jared Price, Screened: 2000; 117004 (Box 71, Folder ID: 143.0504)
      Old number: 00-179
      Director: Black, Dustin Lance
    - Title: Light My Fire, Screened: 2000; 117003 (Box 71, Folder ID: 143.0505)
      Old number: 00-053
      Director: Bruce, Susan
    - Title: Herrmann Project, Screened: 2000; 117002 (Box 71, Folder ID: 143.0507)
    - Title: Huge (Press Screener), Screened: 2000; 117001 (Box 71, Folder ID: 143.0508)
      Director: Alberto Ferraras, Andrea Hereford, Barbara Sanon, Diana Dawson, Draper Shreeve, Stephen Kijak, Ira Sachs, Holly Becker, Jane Young, Jerry Kolber, John Bruce, Jon Schluenz, Laura Comerford, Matt Brown, Michelle Groskopf,etc.
    - Title: Schizophrenia Circa 1986, Screened: 2000; 117000 (Box 71, Folder ID: 143.0509)
      Old number: 00-093
      Director: Vitale, Jeanne
    - Title: 24 Frame News: Episode 80, Screened: 2000; 116999 (Box 71, Folder ID: 143.1478)
    - Title: 24 Frame News: Episode 80, Screened: 2000; 116998 (Box 71, Folder ID: 143.1479)
    - Title: Zen Pussy: A Meditation on Eleven Vulvas, Screened: [1999]; 116997 (Box 71, Folder ID: 143.1498)
      Old number: 00-050
      Director: Sprinkle, Annie and Joseph Kramer
    - Title: Tell Me Who Ruby Was, Screened: 2000; 116996 (Box 71, Folder ID: 143.1559)
      Old number: 00-023
  - Subseries J: Grants/Fundraising/Advertising (see also Oversize series), 116993
    - Grants/fundraising - Fund Raising Day in New York, 2000; 116994 (Box 15, Folder 1323)
- SERIES XV: 2001, 116882
  This series contains materials pertaining to the fifteenth year of the Festival. Subseries B (correspondence), subseries D (electronic database), subseries F (special programs), subseries H (ticket sales), subseries I (outreach), and subseries J (grants/fundraising) do not exist for this year.
  - Subseries A: Administrative Files, 116989
    - Expenses - Color Edge receipt, 2001; 116991 (Box 15, Folder 1325)
    - Programming - Program guide, 2001; 116990 (Box 15, Folder 1326)
  - Subseries C: Entry Forms/Press Kits, 116987
    - Entry forms - misc., 2001; 116988 (Box 15, Folder 1327)
  - Subseries E: Press/Promotion/Posters, 116984
    - Festival flyers, 2001; 116986 (Box 15, Folder 1328)
    - Festival postcards, 2001; 116985 (Box 15, Folder 1329)
  - Subseries G: Media, 116883
    - Title: My Sweet Prince Charming, Screened: 2001; 116983 (Box 72, Folder ID: 143.0488)
      Old number: 01-112
      Director: G, Lisa
    - Title: Even Blue, Screened: 2001; 116982 (Box 72, Folder ID: 143.0506)
      Old number: 01-206
      Director: English, Ryan
    - Title: Bedtime Stories, Screened: 2001; 116981 (Box 72, Folder ID: 143.0510)
      Old number: 01-111
      Director: Daschbach, John
    - Title: Cruise Control, Screened: 2001; 116980 (Box 72, Folder ID: 143.0511)
      Old number: 01-144
      Director: Ferber, Lawrence
    - Title: Descend to the Ocean, Screened: 2001; 116979 (Box 72, Folder ID: 143.0512)
      Old number: 01-031
      Director: Verso, Nicholas
    - Title: Body Burden, Screened: 2001; 116978 (Box 72, Folder ID: 143.0513)
      Old number: 01-125
      Director: Quyeras, France
    - Title: Planetarium, Screened: 2001; 116977 (Box 72, Folder ID: 143.0514)
      Old number: 01-002
    - Title: Casualty, Screened: 2001; 116976 (Box 72, Folder ID: 143.0515)
      Old number: 01-259
      Director: Wilson, Andy Abrahams
    - Title: Lake Ivan Exists: Starfield (episode #37), Screened: 2001; 116975 (Box 72, Folder ID: 143.0516)
      Old number: 01-073
      Director: Finkelstein, David
    - Title: Shoplifting Chanel, Screened: [2001]; 116974 (Box 72, Folder ID: 143.0517)
      Old number: 01-045
      Director: Cohn, Marya
    - Title: GHOST Limb Films: The Trailer, Screened: [2001]; 116973 (Box 72, Folder ID: 143.0518)
      Old number: 01-102
    - Title: Verite, Screened: 2001; 116972 (Box 72, Folder ID: 143.0519)
      Old number: 01-171, 518
      Director: Farinha, Marios
    - Title: Audit, Screened: 2001; 116971 (Box 72, Folder ID: 143.0520)
      Old number: 01-104
      Director: To, Brian
    - Title: Monogamous Slut, Screened: [2001]; 116970 (Box 72, Folder ID: 143.0521)
      Old number: 01-092
      Director: Goldman, Julie and Erin Greenwell
    - Title: Not Quite, Screened: [2001]; 116969 (Box 72, Folder ID: 143.0522)
      Director: Richards, Liz
    - Title: Accidental Insolence, Screened: 2001; 116968 (Box 72, Folder ID: 143.0523)
      Director: Anchor, Kristen
    - Title: [1.]--Beautiful Bones [2.]--Auto Window, Screened: 2001; 116967 (Box 72, Folder ID: 143.0524)
      Old number: 01-165, 209, 01-166, 208
      Director: Wolf, Matt
    - Title: The Travelogue, Screened: 2001; 116966 (Box 72, Folder ID: 143.0525)
      Old number: 01-103
      Distributor: additional credits: ghost limb films
    - Title: Journey Intersex, Screened: 2001; 116965 (Box 72, Folder ID: 143.0526)
      Old number: 01-202
      Director: Volcano, Del LaGrace
    - Title: Hope Is the Thing With Feathers, Screened: 2000; 116964 (Box 72, Folder ID: 143.0527)
      Old number: 01-260
    - Title: Directing Demo Reel: [1.]-- The Visit [2.]-- The Yellow Wallpaper [3.]-- What is Life, Screened:[2001]; 116963 (Box 73, Folder ID: 143.0528)
      Old number: 01-162, 01-163, 01-164
    - Title: Ciao / Ciao, Screened: 2001; 116962 (Box 73, Folder ID: 143.0529)
      Old number: 01-138
      Director: Irving, Michelle
    - Title: The Sleeping Man (L'Uomo Che Dorme), Screened: 2001; 116961 (Box 73, Folder ID: 143.0530)
      Old number: 01-258
      Director: Angeli, Peitor
    - Title: Helpless Maiden Makes an "I" Statement, Screened: 2001; 116960 (Box 73, Folder ID: 143.0531)
      Director: Cuthand, Thirza
    - Title: Soda Pop, Screened: 2001; 116959 (Box 73, Folder ID: 143.0532)
      Old number: 01-007
    - Title: Man Meets Bull, Screened: 2001; 116958 (Box 73, Folder ID: 143.0533)
      Old number: 01-157
      Director: Lasselle, Juli C.
    - Title: Strange News from Another Star, Screened: 2001; 116957 (Box 73, Folder ID: 143.0534)
      Old number: 01-128
      Director: Nielson, Jason
    - Title: Summer Light, Screened: 2001; 116956 (Box 73, Folder ID: 143.0535)
      Old number: 01-174
      Director: Walker, Aaron
    - Title: Drama Queen, Screened: 2001; 116955 (Box 73, Folder ID: 143.0536)
      Old number: 01-052
      Director: Ragsdale, Georgia
    - Title: Hole, Screened: 2001; 116954 (Box 73, Folder ID: 143.0537)
      Director: Cornell, Clare and Rodney Buxton
    - Title: Divine Liquor, Screened: 2001; 116953 (Box 73, Folder ID: 143.0538)
      Old number: 01-147
      Director: Parker, Canaan
    - Title: Phallocy, Screened: 2001; 116952 (Box 73, Folder ID: 143.0539)
      Old number: 01-050
      Director: Sennett, Jay